By the way, Jeff
mentioned that we
had an IAP pass that starts
during IAP for freshmen
and a spring class that's open
to everybody at the institute.
So if you're not a freshman,
you can come to the lottery.
The lottery is for
all of our classes,
are shown on the
Glass Lab website.
And I think we're
going to be doing
the lottery for the spring
for the IAP class in November
late this month, and then the
spring class will probably
be sometime in January,
and it starts in March.
OK, ready?
Five, four, three, two, one.
[INAUDIBLE] will even
have some more energy.
Thanks, Peter.
[APPLAUSE]
That was awesome,
and I actually do
have a high-speed video of it,
so I'll show that to you now.
And again, so if you have
questions about glass,
if you want to watch--
Peter can make animals for
you, I think, on request.
Oh, this guy.
But anyway, thanks a lot,
Peter, for coming by.
As you know, I'm a big believer
in hands on, seeing things.
Can we pass-- is this--
no.
Well, your call.
Just don't eat it.